Guide to the Sterling Law Buildings, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sterling Law Buildings, Yale University, photographs
1930-1969
RU 613
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.75
The records consist of pictures documenting the construction of Sterling Law Buildings at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of pictures documenting the construction of Sterling Law Buildings at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views.
College buildings -- Design and construction; Photographs; Sterling Law Buildings (New Haven, Conn.); Yale Law School; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings
- Photographs, Series I
  - Construction
    - 1930 Jan-1931 Mar (interior views) (Box 1, Folder 1 - 15)
    - General construction, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Repair work (?), 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Exterior views, 1930s-1960s (Box 1, Folder 18 - 19)
  - Interior views (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Plans and drawings (prints of) (Box 1, Folder 21 - 22)
  - Library renovation
    - Carrels (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Duct work (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Mechanical room (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Stacks (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Stairways (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Oversize, 1930s-1960s (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
  - Oversize view (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Transparencies (includes the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscripts Library) (Box 4)